https://www.realworldtech.com/privacy-policy/

Real World Tech LoginCloudMobileGraphicsChipsSoftware CPUsGPUsSemiconductorsStrategyForumsPrivacy Policy
Last Revised 6/27/2012
The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that Real World Insights, LLC treats the information you provide while using www.realworldtech.com (“Website”).
It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You can access the Privacy Policy any time at http://www.realworldtech.com/privacy-policy. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy.
If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.
This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.
In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our User Agreement. Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.
This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.Information Collected
Real World Tech does not collect personally identifiable information, except when such information is voluntarily submitted by the user.
We will not sell, rent or share any such personally identifiable information with any third parties.
Like many websites, we automatically log non-personally identifiable information about visits to our websites; this information is used internally e.g. usage statistics, and is not shared with third parties.Cookies
Real World Tech may place cookies on your computer to track usage patterns, control ad display, handle registration and login to the website, etc.
As a reminder, you may always disable cookies through your browser, although this may negatively impact your experience.Third Parties
Real World Tech works with third party vendors to deliver advertising, analyze user behavior, etc.
These third parties may place cookies on your computer and track non-personally identifiable information to help us improve our user experience, deliver relevant advertising or services.
These third party cookies are governed by our partners privacy and security policies.Acceptance of Terms
By using www.realworldtech.com, you indicate your acceptance of this website privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site.
Your continued use of www.realworldtech.com following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.
Should you have any questions regarding privacy or legal policies, please contact us.Editor’s PicksThe Spider and the MountainBy Paul DeMoneIntel’s Sandy Bridge MicroarchitectureBy David KanterSilvermont, Intel’s Low Power ArchitectureBy David KanterRWT on TwitterHappy anniversary to the whole RWT community, which is now 24 years old! We are thrilled to still have lively discu… https://t.co/RoCe4FACuo about 4 months agoVendors brag about the transistor count of their design. However, transistor count, density varies based on the des… https://t.co/9xiilcfvh1 about 6 months agoRT @rwt: Power delivery is one of the most significant challenges in modern processors. In this article we discuss system power delivery go… about 7 months ago@RWTAbout UsContact UsReprintsAdvertise at RWTWrite for UsPrivacy PolicyForum GuidelinesMembershipTOS
Copyright © 1996-2020 Real World Tech · All Rights Reserved ·
